Guide to the New York University Archives Photograph Collection PHOTO.00001
New York University Archives
- Special Collections
  - Alumni Federation (Box 408, Box 409, Box 410)
  - Freedom's World Exhibition (Box 431)
- Special Events
  - General Pershing and Chancellor Brown, 1925
    - General Pershing and Chancellor Brown 1 -- Negative, 1925 (Item 1)
    - General Pershing and Chancellor Brown 2 -- Negative, 1925 (Item 2)
    - General Pershing and Chancellor Brown 3 -- Negative, 1925 (Item 3)
    - General Pershing and Chancellor Brown 4 -- Negative, 1925 (Item 4)
    - General Pershing and Chancellor Brown 5 -- Negative, 1925 (Item 5)
    - General Pershing and Chancellor Brown 6 -- Negative, 1925 (Item 6)
  - Founders Day, 90th Anniversary, 1921
    - Founders Day, 90th Anniversary 1 -- Negative, 1921 (Item 7)
    - Founders Day, 90th Anniversary 2 -- Negative, 1921 (Item 8)
  - Marshall Foch -- Negative, 1921 (Item 40)
  - 6th Annual Memorial Service - Heights Alumni Dinner (Box 355)
  - American Association of University Presidents - Baroness Zerilli (Box 356)
  - Beauty Pageant - Chancellor's Service Award (Box 357)
  - Chancellor's Service Award - Conference, various (Box 358)
  - Commercial Shoot - Courant Institute (Box 359)
  - Dean's Day - For Whom the Bell Tolls (Box 360)
  - Founders Day - Global Initiative Trip (Box 361)
  - Global Initiative Trip - International Festival (Box 362)
  - Hertsberg Lecture - Lecture, Phelps (Box 363)
  - Lecture, Reilly - Meeting, Humanities Council (Box 364)
  - Mortgage - One to One (Box 365)
  - Parents Day - Silverstein Scholarships (Box 366)
  - Royal Shakespeare Company at NYU - Visit, Foreign Dignitaries (Box 367)
  - Visit, Foreign Dignitaries - Typhoid Inoculation (Box 368)
  - Miscellaneous 1980s events (Box 369, Box 370, Box 371, Box 372, Box 373)
  - Miscellaneous 1990s events - Dean Daley (Box 374)
  - Miscellaneous 2000s events (Box 375)
- Sports/Athletics
  - Baseball Team, 1931 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Administration - Baseball (Box 258, Box 259, Box 260, Box 261)
  - Basketball (Box 262, Box 263, Box 264, Box 265, Box 266, Box 267, Box 268, Box 269)
  - Ballroom Dancing - Fencing, First Aid (Box 270, Box 271, Box 272)
  - Basketball Team, 1909 (Box Shared University Archives 004, Folder 13)
  - Football (Box 273, Box 274)
  - Golf - Promotional Material (Box 275)
  - Racquetball - Soccer (Box 276)
  - Soccer (Box 277)
  - Sports Clinic - Swimming (Box 278, Box 279)
  - Table Tennis - Tennis (Box 280)
  - Track and Field (Box 281, Box 282, Box 283)
  - Trophy - Weehawken Athletic Field (Box 284)
  - Oversized and Framed Photos (Box 285)
- Steinhardt School of Culture, Education, and Human Development
  - Arts and Crafts - Buildings, interiors (Box 478)
  - Children - Classes (Box 64)
  - Classes (Box 65)
  - Clinic for Learning - HEOP (Box 66)
  - Home Economics - Musical Therapy (Box 67)
  - Nursing - Nutrition (Box 68)
  - Occupational Safety - Rehabilitation (Box 69)
  - Sculpture - Telecommunications (Box 70)
  - Theatre, Educational, Miscellaneous prints - Summer Musical Theatre (Box 71)
  - Theatre, Educational, "In a Minor Key" - "Don Pasquale" (Box 72)
  - Theatre, Educational, "Wonderful Town" - "Cabaret" (Box 73)
  - Physical Education, Camp, Lake Sebago (Box 74, Box 75, Box 76, Box 77, Box 78, Box 79, Box 80, Box 81, Box 82, Box 83)
  - Puerto Rican Teachers - United Nations Institute (Box 84)
  - Special Events (Box 85)
  - Summer School (Box 86)
  - Class Scenes - Contacts (Box 87)
  - Contacts (Box 88)
- Stern School of Business (Graduate)
  - Buildings - NIchols Hall (Box 27)
  - Nichols Hall, Construction - NIchols Hall, Exteriors (Box 28)
  - Nichols and Merril Hall - Tisch Hall (Box 29)
  - Administration - Trial Evidence, Nichols building violation (Box 30)
  - Classes (Box 31)
  - Commencement - Trial evidence, Nichols building violation (Box 32)
  - BPA/GBA Faculty Contracts - Faculty teaching (Box 33)
  - Library - Symposia (Box 34)
  - Special Events, general (Box 35)
  - Special Events, general - 1980s+1990s negatives (Box 36)
  - Special Events, 50th Anniversary - Special Events, Taggert, Dean, Memorial Service (Box 37)
- Stern School of Business (Undergraduate)
  - Administration meeting - Classes and students (Box 38)
  - Classes and students - Classroom Blueprint (Box 39)
  - Clubs - Japan Center (Box 40)
  - Manhattanville, Campus - Seminar Classes (Box 41)
  - Special events, general (Box 42)
  - Special events, general (Box 43)
  - Special events, Class of 1914 dinner - Special Events, Reception in honor of Theodore R. Racoosin (Box 44)
  - Contacts: Special events - Negatives, BPA Yearbook (Box 45)
  - Contacts: Special events - Leather Bound Scrapbooks donated by Dean Abraham L. Gitlow (Box 46)
  - Tisch Hall Groundbreaking Ceremony (Box 47)
  - Special Events Leather Bound Scrapbooks - The Eleventh Charles C. Moskowitz Lecture (Box 48)
  - Special Events Leather Bound Scrapbooks - Tisch Hall Dedication (Box 49)
  - Retailing, School of (Box 170)
- Student Life
  - Accounting Club - Bun (Box 286)
  - Campus Scenes (Box 287, Box 288, Box 289, Box 290, Box 291, Box 292)
  - Cane Rush - College Bowl (Box 293)
  - Colonnade Board - Dormitories (Box 294)
  - Dramatic Society - Eucleian Literary Society (Box 295)
  - Fall Festival - Freshmen (Box 296)
  - Fraternities (Box 297, Box 298)
  - Pi Lambda Theta (Box 299)
  - Gay Organizations/Protests, 1970 (Box 300)
    - Gay Pride Parade - Central Park, 1970; wsp_gv_8_4_01; color (photograph), 4 x 4 inches (Box 300)
  - Gavel Club - Guitar Contest (Box 300)
  - Ice Skating - LUCHA (Box 301)
  - Management Club - Pit Day (Box 302)
  - Press Club - Student Portraits (Box 303)
  - Student Portraits (Box 304, Box 305)
  - Protests (Box 306, Box 307, Box 308, Box 309, Box 310, Box 311)
  - Publications, staff - Sororities (Box 312)
  - Sororities - Student Pranks (Box 313)
  - Students Union Office - Wall Street Organization (Box 314)
  - Students in WSP - Youth Leadership Training Program (Box 315)
- Tisch School of the Arts
  - Advisement - Classroom Scenes (Box 1)
  - Communication Arts - Dressing Room (Box 2)
  - Dance Classes (Box 3)
  - Dance performances (Box 4)
  - Dance contacts (Box 5)
  - Dean's office - Dramatic writing (Box 6)
  - Drama-contact prints (Box 7)
  - Drama performances - Film Faculty (Box 8)
  - Film Faculty - Future Filmmakers Program (Box 9)
  - Film and TV contacts (Box 10)
  - Film and Television program - Graduate Acting Program Workshops (Box 11)
  - Make-up class - Movie stills (Box 12)
  - Movement class - Singing (Box 13)
  - Special events (Box 14)
  - Contacts-Stage Design - Theatre Design (Box 15)
- University Heights
  - Nichols Hall -- Negative, 1928 (Item 22)
  - Philosophy Hall -- Negative, 1922 (Item 27)
  - Private Houses, Kimball -- Negative, 1924 (Item 30)
  - Brown House -- Negative, 1925 (Item 28)
  - University College from River -- Negative, 1921 (Item 29)
  - Electrolier at Library -- Negative, 1922 (Item 31)
  - Gould Library Doors
    - Gould Library Doors 1 -- Negative, 1921 (Item 33)
    - Gould Library Doors 2 -- Negative, 1921 (Item 38)
    - Gould Library Doors 3 -- Negative, undated (Item 48)
  - Graduate Hall
    - Graduate Hall -- Negative, 1925 (Item 24)
    - Graduate Hall -- Negative, 1926 (Item 35)
  - Biological Laboratories -- Negative, 1924 (Item 34)
  - Hall of Philosophy -- Negative, 1926 (Item 36)
  - University Heights Campus Bridge -- Negative, 1926 (Item 39)
  - Eastman Pyrometal Tank
    - Eastman Pyrometal Tank 1 -- Negative, 1926 (Item 41)
    - Eastman Pyrometal Tank 2 -- Negative, 1928 (Item 53)
  - Fountain -- Negative, 1921 (Item 42)
  - Lipton Flag Mast -- Negative, 1925 (Item 44)
  - Gould Memorial Library
    - Gould Memorial Library 1 -- Negative, undated (Item 45)
    - Gould Memorial Library 2 -- Negative, undated (Item 46)
    - Gould Memorial Library 3 -- Negative, undated (Item 47)
  - Gould Hall -- Negative, undated (Item 49)
  - University Heights Neighborhood -- Negative, 1926 (Item 51)
  - University Heights Neighborhood from Hall of Fame -- Negative, 1926 (Item 52)
  - Aerial View of University Heights Campus and Neighborhood 1 -- Negative, 1938
  - Aerial View of University Heights Campus and Neighborhood 2 -- Negative, undated
  - Power House -- Negative, 1926 (Item 55)
  - South Hall
    - South Hall 1 -- Negative, 1926 (Item 56)
    - South Hall 2 -- Negative, 1926 (Item 57)
  - New Grandstand -- Negative, 1925 (Item 61)
  - General Views - unidentified (Box 427)
  - Gould Library (Box 428)
  - Oversized - Gould Student Center (Box 429)
  - Dean Thorndike Saville - General Views (Box 430)
  - General Views (Box 432, Box 434)
  - Aerial views (Box 433, Box 435)
  - Aerospace laboratory - Biology Laboratories (Box 436)
  - Bliss Engineering Laboratory - Engineering WW II Photo Album (Box 437)
  - Engineering - Gould Hall of Technology (Box 438)
  - Gould Library, Exteriors - Gould Library, Stanford White Memorial Doors (Box 476)
  - Gould Library interiors (Box 439)
  - Gould Library, exteriors - Gould House (Box 440)
  - Gould Student Center (Box 441)
  - Green Laboratory - Guggenheim School of Aeronautics (Box 442)
  - Gymnasium (Box 443)
  - Hall of Fame (Box 444)
  - Hall of Fame (Box 445, Box 446, Box 447, Box 448, Box 449)
  - Havermeyer Hall of Chemistry - Knoop Sculpture (Box 450)
  - Laboratories - Machinery (Box 451)
  - Mali Estate (Box 452)
  - Neighborhood - Negatives (Box 453)
  - Nichols Building (Box 454)
  - Plans - Silver Residence Hall (Box 455)
  - Sonic Boom Lab - YMCA (Box 456)
  - Schwab House and Estate (Box 457)
  - World War II Engineering album (Box 458)
- Vanderbilt Hall/Law School
  - Artist's renderings - Exteriors (Box 251, Box 252, Box 253)
- Wagner Graduate School of Public Service
  - Special Events - Students (Box 50)
- Weinstein Center for Student Living
  - Construction site - Sculpture (Box 254, Box 255, Box 256, Box 257)
- Non-NYU Subjects
  - Landmark Buildings (Box 459)
  - Aerial views of NYC - Atomic Bomb Drill (Box 460)
  - Barnes & Noble - City Skylines (Box 461)
  - City Scenes (Box 462, Box 463)
  - Clinton Court - Garment District (Box 464)
  - Goulandris Museum - Manhattan street scenes (Box 465)
  - Map of NYC - NY Police (Box 466)
  - NYPL - Presidents (Box 467)
  - Radio City Music Hall - Soho (Box 468)
  - South Church - Telephones (Box 469)
  - Theatre District - Yellow Brick Road (Box 470)
- Miscellaneous
  - Illustrations (Box 472)
  - Digital photos on physical media (Box 474)
  - Separated photos, RG 4.2, RG 9.7 (Box 475)
  - Group photos at an awards ceremony, undated (Box Shared University Archives 042, Folder 1)
  - Photograph of building labeled "To Julius Silver with gratitude and appreciation from the staff of the Institute", undated (Box Shared University Archives 042, Folder 4)
  - Photos pulled for Oliva exhibit (Box 475)
  - Senior Ball, 1934 (Box Shared University Archives 091, Folder 8)